

Contact

Bhawal Jamalpur, Kaliganj, Gazipur +8801316447745 (Work) m0takabbir@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/motakabbir (Linkedin) motakabbir.com (Personal) techsmsbd.com (Blog)

Top Skills

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Illustrator

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Bengali (Native or Bilingual)
Korean (Limited Working)
Hindi (Limited Working)

Certifications

Learning Graphic Design: Layouts Learning Catalog Design Graphic Design Masterclass - Learn GREAT Design by Lindsay Marsh First Step Korean Graphic Design

Motakabbir Hossan

Freelance Graphic Designer

Summary

I am an Engineering Student. I started Graphic design 4 years ago now it became my passion.

I love to work with pixels. I have 3+ years of Graphic Design skills. I am very proficient at Photoshop and

Illustrator. My Linkedin Profile also says that. This proficiency is built by the amount of time I invested in this sector.

I do Print-Design, Marketing & Advertising, Package & Product
Design, Signage Design, Image Retouching, and
also all kinds of Photo treatment

I also have HTML, CSS knowledge with WordPress and JavaScript.

I believe these skills drove me to the right path that I have chosen.

Experience

Glorious Bangladesh Creative Content Creator August 2021 - Present (2 months)

Fiverr

Freelance Graphic Designer April 2016 - Present (5 years 6 months) Dhaka, Bangladesh

Upwork

Graphic Designer March 2015 - Present (6 years 7 months)

Freelancer.com
Freelance Graphic Designer
April 2016 - Present (5 years 6 months)
Dhaka, Bangladesh

techSMSBD

Co-Founder Co-Administrator and Content Creator November 2015 - Present (5 years 11 months)

Dhaka, Bangladesh

Education

Shyamoli Textile Engineering College

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electrical and Electronics Engineering · (January 2020 - August 2024)

National Ideal School & College

Higher Secondary School Certificate, Science · (June 2017 - July 2019)

Janata Adarsha Bidyapith

ssc, Student Counseling and Personnel Services · (2006 - 2017)